(美国魔法部)
(纽约 1927)
你很开心能够摆脱他吧  我想
You'll be glad to be rid of him, I expect.
我们更希望他能够继续在牢里关着
We'd be more than happy to keep him here in custody.
六个月已经足够了
Six months are enough.
他是时候为他在欧洲犯下的罪行担上责任了
It's time for him to answer for his crimes in Europe.
皮克科瑞主席 斯皮尔曼先生
President Picquery, Mr. Spielman, sir.
犯人已经准备好转移了
Prisoner is secured and ready to travel.
你们把能用的招都用上了
You've thrown everything at him, I see.
这很有必要 他太强大了
It was necessary. He's extremely powerful.
我们换了三次守卫 他嘴皮子非常厉害
We've had to change his guard three times, he's very... persuasive.
所以我们割掉了他的舌头
So we removed his tongue.
格林德沃 格林德沃
Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
全球的巫师界都欠你一个人情 主席女士
The wizarding community worldwide owes you a great debt, Madam President.
不要小看他
Do not underestimate him.
斯皮尔曼先生 我们刚发现他藏起来的魔杖
Mr. Spielman, we found his wand hidden away.
阿伯内西
Abernathy?
我们还找到这个
And we found this.
还油嘴滑舌吗 嗯?
No more silver tongue, hmm?
我的朋友 你加入了一项高尚的事业
You have joined a noble cause, my friend.
安东尼奥 我知道 我知道
I know. I know. I know, Antonio
太饥渴了
So needy.
《神奇动物2：格林德沃之罪》
(英国伦敦)
(英国魔法部)
(三个月后)
他们准备好了 纽特
They're ready for you, Newt.
莉塔
Leta...
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
忒修斯认为我成为魔法部大家族的一员是个很好的主意
Theseus thought it would be good if I became part of the Ministry family.
他真的用了"大家族"这个词吗
Did he actually say the words "Ministry family"?
不愧是他
That sounds like my brother
你没来吃晚餐 忒修斯很失望
Theseus was disappointed you couldn't come to dinner.
每次问你你都没空
Any of the nights we've asked you.
我一直很忙
Well, I've been busy.
他是你的哥哥 纽特
He's your brother, Newt.
他喜欢跟你在一起
He likes spending time with you.
我也是
And so do I.
嘿 皮克 跳进来
Oi, you! Hop in, Pick.
为什么那些奇奇怪怪的生物那么喜欢你
Why do strange creatures love you so much?
-唔  没有什么奇奇怪怪的生物... -只有心胸狭隘的人
-Well, there are no strange creatures... - Only blinkered people!
你说完这个之后被普伦德加斯特留堂了多久
How long did you get in detention for saying that to Prendergast?
好像是一个月吧 那一次
You know, I think it was a month that time.
记得吗 我为了跟你一起还在他桌子底下设了个粪蛋
And I set off a Dung bomb under his desk so I could join you, do you remember?
不是很记得了
No, I actually don't remember that.
你们好啊
Hello.
忒修斯 我们刚才在说纽特会来一起享用晚餐
Theseus. We were just talking about Newt coming for dinner
喔 真的吗
Really? Well...
听着 在我们进去之前 我...
Look, before we go in there I
忒修斯 这都第五次了 我知道程序
It's my fifth attempt, Theseus. I know the form.
这次跟其他的不一样 这次...
This isn't going to be like the other times. This is...
心态尽量放开点 好吗
Just try and keep an open mind, will you?
-然后尽量不要那么... -像我自己
-And maybe a little less. - Like me?
又不会少一块肉
Well, it can't hurt.
嘿 进来吧
Come on. Let's go.
听证会开始
Hearing commences...
你希望我们终止对你国际旅行的禁令 为什么呢
You want an end to the ban on your traveling internationally. Why?
因为我喜欢国际旅行
Because I like to travel internationally.
申请人拒绝合作并刻意回避回答上次国际旅行的原因
Subject uncooperative and evasive on reasons for last international trip.
那次只是一次实地考察
It was a field trip.
我在为我关于神奇动物的书收集资料
So I was collecting material for my book on magical beasts
你毁了半个纽约
You destroyed half of New York.
-不对 实际上有两个方面不正确 -纽特
-No, that's actually factually incorrect on two counts. -Newt.
斯卡曼德先生 显然你很困扰
Mr. Scamander, it's clear you're frustrated and
坦白说, 我们也是
frankly, so are we
折中一点 我们想达成一个协议
In the spirit of compromise, we'd like to make a proposition.
什么样的协议
What kind of proposition?
答应一个条件 委员会就终止你的旅行禁令
The committee will agree to lift your travel ban under one condition.
你加入魔法部
You join the Ministry.
准确来说 加入你哥哥的部门
Specifically, your brother's department.
不行
No.
我觉得忒修斯比较适合做傲罗
I...I think that... Theseus is the Auror
我认为我另有所长
I think my talents lie elsewhere.
斯卡曼德先生 巫师和非巫师世界的和平
Mr. Scamander, The wizarding and non-wizarding
已经持续了一个多世纪了
worlds have been at peace for over a century.
格林德沃想摧毁这份和平
Grindelwald wants to see that peace destroyed.
对于我们社会的某些人来说
And for certain members of our community
他的思想是十分吸引人的
his message is very seductive
很多纯血认为他们生为统治者
Many pure-bloods believe it is their birthright to rule
不只是在巫师界 在麻瓜世界亦是
not only our world but the non-magic world as well.
他们认格林德沃为领导者
They see Grindelwald as their hero,
而格林德沃将这个男孩
and Grindelwald sees this boy
看作能使这一切成为现实的手段
as a means to make this all come true.
抱歉 你说的好像克雷登斯还在世一样
I'm sorry. You're talking about Credence as if he were still here.
纽特 他活了下来
He survived, Newt.
他还活着
He is still alive.
几个月前他离开了纽约
He left New York months ago.
他在欧洲的某个地方 我们不知道确切地点 但是...
He's somewhere in Europe. Where exactly, we don't know, but...
你们希望我去抓他
And you want me to hunt Credence down?
去杀了他?
To kill him?
还是老样子啊 斯卡曼德
Same old Scamander.
他在这里干什么
What's he doing here?
接手软弱的你不敢做的任务
Taking on the job you're too soft to do.
就这样吗?
Is that it?
拒绝通过旅行档案
Travel documentation denied.
纽特
Newt!
你以为我会喜欢格里姆森的主意吗
You think I like the idea of Grimmson any more than you do?
听着 忒修斯 我不想听什么结果胜于手段如何如何
Listen, I don't want to hear how the ends justify the means, Theseus.
你不能再像鸵鸟把自己的头埋在沙子里似的逃避现实
I think you're gonna have to pull your head out of the sand!
啊, 对, 又来了. 多么自私...不负责任...
Okay, right, here we go. What a selfish... irresponsible...
那个时代快来临了 每一个人
You know, the time is coming when everyone's
每一个人 都要选边站
everyone's gonna have to pick a side.
连你也一样
Even you.
我不站边的
I don't do sides.
纽特 纽特
Newt. Newt.
过来
C'mere.
他们时时刻刻都在盯着你
They are watching you.
好吧 先生们
Well, gentlemen.
我想 这代表这份任务 归我了
I assume this means I have the job.
(法国 巴黎)
[法语] 宝贝
[法语] 外面是谁?
彻底清理之后 这里就会变得很舒适了
This will be suitable after a thorough cleanse.
我希望你现在就动身去马戏团
I want you to go to the circus now.
把我的信带给克雷登斯
Give my note to Credence,
开始他的旅程
begin his journey.
等我们赢了 有成千上万的人会逃走
When we've won, they'll flee cities in the millions.
他们得意得够久了
They've had their time.
这些事情不需要我们大声说出来
We don't say such things out loud.
我们只想要自由
We want only freedom.
可以做自己的自由
Freedom to be ourselves.
还要消灭不会魔法的人
To annihilate non-wizards.
不是他们所有人 不全是
Not all of them. Not all.
我们还不至于那么无情
We're not merciless.
任何时候都需要用来干活的牲畜
The beast of burden will always be necessary.
(梅里恩街)
风旋骤卷
Ventus.
邓布利多
Dumbledore.
你非得站在这么显眼的屋顶上吗?
Were the less conspicuous rooftops full, then?
我确实很喜欢欣赏风景
I do enjoy a view.
云雾缥缈
Nebulus.
怎么样了
How was it?
他们仍然坚信是你派我去纽约的
They're still convinced that you sent me to New York.
你说不是我?
You told them I didn't?
是的
Yes.
晚安
Evening.
虽然确实是你
Even though you did.
是你告诉我哪里可以找到那只被交易的雷鸟
You told me where to find that trafficked Thunderbird,
邓布利多 你清楚我会带他回家
Dumbledore. You knew that I would take him home
你也知道我只能用麻瓜的交通工具带他走
and you knew I'd have to take him through a Muggle port.
嗯 我总觉得我和那些有强大魔力的鸟类有亲切感
Well, I've always felt an affinity with the great magical birds..
在我家族中有一个传说
There's a story in my family
邓布利多家族的人有急切需要时 凤凰就会出现
that a phoenix will come to any Dumbledore who is in desperate need.
据说我的曾祖父就有一只 但是自从他去世后
They say my great-great grandfather had one, but that it took flight when he died,
凤凰就再也没有出现过
never to return.
恕我冒昧 教授 我绝对不相信
With all due respect, I don't believe for a minute
这就是你告诉我雷鸟的原因
that's why you told me about the Thunderbird.
(删剪片段)
你为什么要送我去纽约
Why did you send me to New York?
因为我知道格林德沃会试图抓住克雷登斯
Because I knew Grindelwald would try to catch Credence.
你要知道 多年以前 他就预知
He had a vision, you see, many years ago
一个默然者杀死了他最害怕的人
In which an Obscurial killed a man he fears above all others
就是你
You.
我觉得你能消灭格林德沃的武器
I thought you might deprive Grindelwald of his weapon.
不过不是要杀死克雷登斯 而是拯救他
Not by killing Credence, but by saving him.
克雷登斯在巴黎 纽特
Credence is in Paris, Newt.
他在寻找到自己真正的家族
He's trying to trace his real family.
这我信
I take it.
我估计你已听说 关于他真实身分的传闻
You've heard the rumors about who he really is?
并没有
No.
纯血家族认为他是法国一个重要家族最后的血脉
The pure-bloods think he's the last of an important French line,
他们认为 他在婴儿时期就失踪了
a baby whom everyone thought lost
-那不是指莉塔的弟弟吧? -大家是这么想的
- Not Leta's brother? - That's what they're whispering.
无论是不是纯血 我知道
Pure-blood or not, I know this...
默默然是因为缺少关爱而产生的
An Obscurus grows in the absence of love
只能终日与黑暗为伴
as a dark twin, an only friend.
如果克雷登斯真的有亲生的兄弟姐妹能够代替默默然
If Credence has a real brother or sister out there that can take its place,
他也许还有救
he might yet be saved.
不论他在巴黎的何处 若不是身处险境
Wherever Credence is in Paris, he's either in danger
就是会危害他人
or a danger to others.
我们仍然不知道他到底是谁 但是我们必须找到他
We may not know who he is yet, but he needs to be found.
我希望你能找到他
And I rather hoped you might be the one to find him.
这是什么
What's that?
这是我一个老熟人的地址
An address of a very old acquaintance of mine.
这是巴黎的一处安全屋 用魔法进行保护
A safe house in Paris, reinforced with enchantments.
安全屋 我为什么需要在巴黎用安全屋
Safe house? Why would I need a safe house in Paris?
我也希望你用不上 但是凡事总会有意外
One hopes you won't, but should things at some point go terribly wrong
有地方去总是件好事
it's good to have a place to go.
至少能喝杯茶 你懂的
You know, for a cup of tea.
不 不 不 绝对不行
No, no, no, absolutely not.
我被禁止出境旅行 邓布利多
I'm banned from international travel, Dumbledore.
如果我离开英国 他们就会把我丢进阿兹卡班 然后把钥匙丢了
If I leave the country, they will put me in Azkaban and throw away the key.
-你知道为什么我如此喜欢你吗 纽特? -为什么?
-Do you know why I admire you, Newt? -Why?
认识的人里我最喜欢你
More, perhaps, than any man I know?
你不渴望权利
You don't seek power
或者名气
or popularity.
你在乎的 是事物的本身是否正确
You simply ask, is the thing right in itself?
如果是 你会为此不计一切代价
If it is, you do it, no matter the cost.
好吧差不多是这样 邓布利多
That's all very well, Dumbledore
但是请原谅 我想问 为什么你不去?
but, forgive me for asking, why can't you go?
我不能对抗格林德沃
I cannot move against Grindelwald.
只能是你
It has to be you.
好吧 我不怪你
Well, I can't blame you,
如果我是你 我也很可能会拒绝
in your shoes I'd probably refuse too.
-什么... -不早了 晚安 纽特
- What? - It's late. Good evening, Newt
等等 不
Wait. No!
哦 不会吧
Oh, come on.
邓布利多
Dumbledore.
邦缇
Bunty!
邦缇 嗅嗅宝宝又跑出来了
Bunty, the baby Nifflers are loose again!
好样的
Well done
我很抱歉 纽特
I'm so sorry, Newt.
他们肯定是趁我清理卜鸟的时候溜了
They must have picked the lock while I was cleaning out the Augureys
没关系
Not to worry.
差不多都喂了 给平奇滴了鼻液 然后
I've fed nearly everyone, Pinky's had his nose drops, and
艾尔西呢
And Elsie?
艾尔西的粪便也快要正常了
Elsie's droppings are nearly normal again.
非常好
Wonderful.
你现在可以下班了...
You can clock off now...
-我跟你说过把马形水怪交给我 -伤口还需要擦药膏
- I told you to leave the Kelpie to me. - That wound needs more ointment.
我不想你失去你的手指
I don't want you losing fingers over it.
说真的 快回去吧 邦缇
Seriously, you go home now, Bunty.
你肯定累坏了
You must be exhausted.
两个人一起对付马形水怪会更容易
You know the Kelpie's easier with two.
要不要把衬衫脱了?
Perhaps you should take off your shirt?
别担心
Don't worry,
我马上就能弄干
I'll dry off quickly enough.
看起来有人需要宣泄一下感情 药膏 邦缇
Someone needed to let off some steam. Ointment, Bunty?
你再敢咬邦缇 我就要给你点颜色看看了 先生
You bite Bunty again and there'll be trouble, mister.
什么声音?
What was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我想你真的该回家了 邦缇
But I want you to go home now, Bunty.
需要我叫魔法部吗?
Shall I call the Ministry?
不 我需要你回家 请回吧
No, I want you to go home. Please.
如果可以 请把东西给我
If you could just give it to me...
亲爱的 麻烦把它给我
Honey, if you could just give it to me.
-他不会介意的 拿着
- He doesn't care. Hold it.
那就把它给我吧
If you could just give it to me.
嘿...
Hey...
纽特！到这里来 你这个小疯子
NEWT! Get over here, you maniac.
我们希望你不会介意 纽特 我们擅自进来了...
We hope you don't mind, Newt? We let ourselves in...
外面在下雨 倾盆大雨
it's raining out there-cats and dogs!
伦敦真冷
London's cold!
但是你不是应该一忘皆空了吗！
But you were supposed to have been Obliviated!
我知道 但这没用 伙计
I know! It didn't work, pal.
我是说 你说过 那个毒液只会消除不好的记忆
I mean, you said it, the potion only erases bad memories.
我压根儿没有
I didn't have any.
别误会 我是有一些奇怪的记忆
I mean, don't get me wrong, I had some weird ones...
但是这个天使...
but this angel...
这位天使把我遗忘的部分又重新告诉我了
this angel over here, she filled me in on all the bad parts.
所以我们现在在这里了
And here we are, I guess, huh?
这太棒了
This is wonderful!
等等 那是...
Wait... is it...
蒂娜 蒂娜
Tina? Tina?
哦 亲爱的 这里只有我们
Oh it's just us, honey.
我和雅各布
Me and Jacob.
你不介意我给大家做晚餐吧 嗯?
Why don't I make us some dinner, huh?
好棒！
Yes!
嗨,甜心
Hey, hon
蒂娜和我都不怎么说话了
Tina and I aren't talking.
为什么？
Why?
嗯...你知道 她发现了我和雅各布
Oh well, you know, she found out about Jacob and
一直在见面 她不喜欢我们这样
I seeing each other and she didn't like it,
因为"法律"
cause of the "law."
不许...不许和麻鸡约会
Not allowed oops, not allowed to date No-Majs,
不许和他们结婚 没完没了
not allowed to marry them blah, blah, blah.
并且 因为你 她总是很容易感到烦躁
Well, she was all in a tizzy anyway, 'cause of you.
我？
Me?
对 就你 纽特
Yeah, you, Newt
《意乱情迷》上都写了
It was in Spellbound
在这 我替你带来了
Here, I brought it for you
纽特·斯卡曼德和未婚妻莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Newt Scamander and fiancee Leta Lestrange
哥哥忒修斯的伴侣未知
Brother Thesus and unknown woman
不 要娶莉塔的是忒修斯不是我
No. So Thesus is marrying Leta, not me.
哦天啊
Oh. Oh dear.
但是
Well,
蒂娜看到消息后 就开始跟别人约会了
So Tina read that, and she started dating someone else
是个傲罗 叫阿喀琉斯·托利弗
He's an auror. His name is Achilles Tolliver
托利佛
Tolliver
总之 我们来这里真的很高兴 纽特
ANYWAY, we are really excited to be here Newt.
这次旅行对我们来说很特别
This is a special trip for us.
雅各布和我
You see, Jacob and I
就要结婚啦
We're getting married!
和雅各布结婚
Marry Jacob
你对他施法了是吗
You've enchanted him, haven't you?
什么
What?
我没有
I have not.
你能不能别读我心
Will you stop reading my mind?
奎妮 你违背他的意愿带他来这里的
Queenie, you've brought him here against his will.
噢 你怎么能这么说 看看他
Oh, that is an outrageous accusation. Look at him.
他现在特别开心
He's just happy.
那你不会介意我
Then you won't mind if I...
千万别
Please don't!
奎妮 如果他想结婚的话你没什么好怕的
Queenie, you've got nothing to fear if he wants to get married.
我们可以让他恢复正常 然后自己告诉我们
We can just lift the enchantment... and he can tell us himself.
你那是什么
What you got there?
你要干什么 你要用它干什么 斯卡曼德先生
Whatchu gonna do? Whatchu gonna do with that, Mr. Scamander?
咒术解除
Surgito.
雅各布 恭喜你的订婚
Congratulations on your engagement, Jacob.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
哦不 你没有
Oh no, you didn't.
奎儿 等下
Queen. A second.
奎妮
Queenie!
很高兴见到你
It's very nice to see you.
我现在到底在哪里
Where the hell am I right now?
额 伦敦
Uh, uh, London.
噢 我一直想来的
Oh! I always wanted to go here!
奎妮
Queenie!
噢 奎妮 亲爱的
Oh Queenie, honey.
等等 我只是想问一下 你准备什么时候让我恢复正常 当我们有了五个孩子以后吗
Well, I'm just curious, when were you going to wake me up? After we'd had five kids?
-我想嫁给你有错吗 -好吧
- Why is it wrong to want to marry you? - Okay.
想要个家庭有错吗
To wanna have a family?
我只想拥有其他人有的东西 就这些
I just want what everyone else has, that's all.
好的 等等 我们都讨论过这个 快几百万次了
Okay, wait.. We talked about this, like, a million times.
如果他们发现我们两个结婚的话 他们会把你扔进监狱的 亲爱的
If we get married and they find out, they're gonna throw you in jail, sweetheart.
我不能让这发生
I can't have that.
他们不喜欢像我这样的人和像你这样的人通婚
They don't like people like me marrying people like you.
我不是个巫师 只是个普通人
I ain't a wizard. I'm just me.
他们这边很包容 我们可以光明正大结婚的
They're really progressive here, and they'll let us get married properly.
亲爱的 你不需要对我施法
Sweetheart, you don't need to enchant me.
我早已为你着迷
I'm already enchanted!
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
-真的吗 -真的
- Yeah?? - Yeah.
但我不能让你这样冒险 你知道吗
But I can't have you risking everything like this, you know?
你不给我任何选择 亲爱的
You're not giving us a choice, sweetheart.
你也没有给我一个选择
You're not givin' me a choice.
我们两个必须有一个人需要勇敢起来 然后你还是个懦夫
One of us had to be brave, and you were being a coward!
我是个懦夫
I was being a coward?
如果我是个懦夫 你就是个
If I'm a coward, you're...
疯子
Crazy
我没这么说
I didn't say it...
-你不需要说出口 -我不是那个意思 亲爱的
- You didn't have to. - No, I didn't mean it, sweetheart.
不 你就是那个意思
Yeah, you did.
我要去见我姐姐
I'm gonna go see my sister.
-好 去见你姐姐去吧 - 好
-Fine. See your sister. - Fine.
不,等等
No! Wait!
不,奎妮
Queenie! No! Queenie!
我不是这个意思
I didn't mean it.
我什么也没说
I didn't say nothing.
恢复如初
Papyrus Reparo
巴黎
PARIS
我亲爱的奎妮 这可真是个美丽的城市
My dear Queenie, what a beautiful city.
我在想你 蒂娜
I'm thinking of you. Tina.
嘿 纽特
Hey, Newt?
在下面 雅各布 我马上过去
Down here, Jacob. I'll be with you in a second.
我自己的麻烦就不少了
I got my own problems.
邦缇 别忘了给帕特里克喂药
BUNTY! DON'T FORGET TO GIVE PATRICK PELLETS.
（蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩成为傲罗）
Tina Goldstein pointed as auror
奎妮留下一张明信片
Queenie left a postcard.
蒂娜在巴黎找克雷登斯
Tina's in Paris looking for Credence.
太棒了
Genius!
奎妮会直接去找蒂娜的
Queenie's gonna go straight for Tina.
好的 我们要去法国了 兄弟
Okay, we're going to France, pal!
- 等下 我去拿我的夹克 - 我拿好了
- Hold on. I'll get my jacket. - I've got it
棒极了
Oh. Beautiful.
(删剪片段)
来吧
Come on
我觉得叫邦缇应付这些生物和一堆新生儿
I don't think it's reasonable to ask Bunty to cope with everyone here
不太合理,所以...
and a bunch of newborns, so...
你疯了吗?
Are you insane?
你现在要打包嗅嗅了吗?
You're gonna pack the nifflers now?
-进去吧 -记得上次发生什么事吗?
- In you hop. - Remember what happened last time?
我们把锁修好了
We fixed the lock.
现在没我允许什么都跑不出来
So nothing gets out without my say-so
快来吧
Come on.
快点啦
Get a move on.
行吧 项链飞来
All right then. Accio necklace
现在你做个好榜样
Now you set a good example
（邦缇 我带了嗅嗅去巴黎 --纽特）
BUNTY, GONE TO PARIS. HAVE TAKEN NIFFLERS WITH ME. NEWT.
纳吉尼
Nagini.
克雷登斯
Credence.
我想我知道她在哪里
I think I know where she is.
我们今晚逃走
We escape tonight.
嘿
Hey.
我跟你说过离她远点
I've told you to stay away from her, boy.
我说过你可以休息了吗
Did I say you could take a break?
去给河童洗澡
Clean out the Kappa.
你 去做准备
And you, get ready!
接下来 我们这个精奇古怪的表演里
Next in our little show of freaks and oddities...
我要呈现给各位的
I present to you...
是一个血咒宿主
a Maledictus!
它曾经被困在印度尼西亚的森林里
Once trapped in the jungles of Indonesia,
身上背负着血咒
she is the carrier of a blood curse.
像她这样的生物 一生的宿命
Such Under-beings are destined, through the course of their lives...
注定是会永远转变成野兽的
to turn permanently into beasts.
看看她
But look at her.
多么漂亮 是不是
So beautiful, yes?
如此诱人
So desirable.
但是很快 她会永远被困在一副截然不同的躯体里了
But soon she will be trapped forever in a very different body.
每晚当她沉睡时,女士们和先生们
Every night, when she sleeps, mesdames et messieurs...
她都会变成...
She is forced to become...
久而久之 她就再也变不回来了
Over time, she will not be able to transform back.
她会永远被困在蛇的躯体之中
She will be forever trapped in the body of a snake.
克雷登斯
Credence!
收拾东西走人 巴黎容不下我们了
Pack it up! Paris is done for us now.
关于和血咒宿主一起的男孩 你都了解些什么
The boy with the Maledictus, what do you know about him?
他在找他的妈妈
He's looking for his mother.
我马戏团里所有的怪胎们觉得他们能回家
All my freaks think they can go home.
好 走了
Okay, let's go.
你看 我觉得我们是因为同一个原因来到马戏团的 先生
Look, I think we were both at the circus for the same reason, monsieur.
我是卡玛 尤瑟夫·卡玛
Kama. Yusuf Kama.
你想得没错
And you think right.
-你想找克雷登斯干什么 -跟你一样的目的
- What do you want with Credence? - The same as you.
说说看
Which is?
证明他的真实身份
To prove who the boy really is.
如果关于他身份的传言属实 那我们算是
If the rumors of his identity are correct, he and I are
远亲
distantly related.
我是我们纯血家族里的最后一名男丁
I am the last male of my pure-blooded line.
若传闻属实 他也是我的族人
And so, if the rumors are correct, is he
你读过泰克 多多纳斯的预言录吗
Have you read The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus?
读过 但那只是诗 不能作为证据
Yeah. But that's poetry, not proof.
我可以给你看看更充分
If I could show you something better
更有说服力的证据 一些能证实他身份的东西
more concrete, something that proves who he is
欧洲和美国的魔法部会让他活下来吗
would the Ministries of Europe and America let him live?
可能会
They might.
那就跟我来吧
Then come.
(删剪片段)
又来了 亚克斯利
Oh no, Yaxley
我讨厌他每次都这样直勾勾地盯着我
I hate the way he makes a beeline for me every time.
没办法 谁让你一直都是屋子里最美的女人呢
Not if you insist on being the most beautiful woman in the room.
你知道他不是这样想的
It's not that and you know it.
亚克斯利的双手沾满了鲜血
It's all blood with Yaxley.
那我去祝贺他一下 我们就可以跳舞了
Let me go and congratulate him and we can dance.
而我保证在这以后今晚都不会跟任何人说一句话
And then I promise I won't say a word to anyone for the rest of the night
-你保证? -我保证
- You promise? - Promise.
抱歉
Sorry
-你最近怎么样 -你这只老狐狸
- How have you been? - You sly dog
是她吗？
Is that her?
是的 你看
It is, look.
她弟弟还活着
Her brother's alive
预言是真的
The prediction is true
她弟弟会带领我们走出阴霾
Her brother would lead us from the shadows
"回来吧 伟大的复仇者 带着水中之翼"
"Return, great avenger, with wings from the water"
莉塔 恭喜你
Congratulations, Leta
你弟弟活下来了
Your brother lives
我们都十分相信这一点
We all truly believe it
所以
So,
克雷登斯 拜尔本
Credence Barebone
差点被他的养母毁掉
Nearly destroyed by the woman who raised him.
但现在他在寻找他的生母
Yet now he seeks the mother who bore him.
他渴望家庭
He's desperate for family.
他渴望被爱
He's desperate for love.
他是我们成功的关键
He's the key to our victory.
我们知道那个男孩在哪 不是吗
Well, we know where the boy is, don't we?
为什么我们不抓了他就走
Why don't we grab him and leave!
他必须自愿来找我 而他也会这么做
He must come to me freely,and he will.
路已经铺好了 他正在顺着它前进
The path has been laid, and he is following it.
这条路会把他带向我的身边
The trail that will lead him to me,
也会向他揭示他古怪而又光荣的身世
and the strange and glorious truth of who he is.
为什么他如此重要
Why is he so important?
谁代表着我们事业最大的威胁
Who represents the greatest threat to our cause?
阿不思·邓布利多
Albus Dumbledore.
如果我让你现在去学校 把他从藏身之处揪出来
If I asked you now to go to the school... where he is
替我杀了他 你愿意吗 克拉尔
hiding and kill him for me, would you do it for me, Krall?
克雷登斯是这世上唯一
Credence is the only entity alive...
能杀死他的人
who can kill him.
你真的认为他可以杀了伟大的...
You really think that he can kill the great...
可以杀了阿不思·邓布利多吗
can kill Albus Dumbledore?
我知道他可以
I know he can.
但克拉尔 当这一切发生时 你还会和我们站在一起吗
But will you be with us when that happens, Krall?
会吗
Will you?
(删剪片段)
万一她不想要我呢
What if she doesn't want me?
好好照顾她吧
Make it happen.
什么
What?
因为我们自由了
Because we are free.
雅各布 那个蒂娜一直在约会的男人
Jacob, that man Tina's been seeing...
别担心 等她见到你 就会想起我们四个人一起的时光
Don't worry, she's gonna see you. And she'll see the four of us together
这就会像纽约那时一样 别担心
it'll be just like New York all over again. Don't worry about it.
-是的 但奎妮说他是个傲罗 -是的 他是个傲罗 那又如何?
- Yes, but he's an Auror, Queenie said? - Yeah, he's an Auror. So what?
别担心他
Don't worry about him.
你觉得我见到她应该对她说什么
What do you think I should say to her, if I see her?
哦,这个还是顺其自然吧
Oh, well, it's best not to plan these things.
你知道的 到时候你想到什么就说什么
You know, you just say whatever comes to you in the moment.
她的眼睛和火蜥蜴一样
She has eyes just like a salamander.
这还是算了
Don't say that.
这样吧 你就直接告诉她你很想她
Nah, look, you just tell her that you missed her.
对 然后你大老远跑到巴黎就是为了找她
Right, and then you came all the way to Paris just to find her.
她会很开心的 然后
She'll love that. And then...
然后告诉她你想她想得失眠了
tell her you're losing sleep at night for thinking of her.
反正不要说任何关于火蜥蜴的事
Just don't say anything about no salamanders, all right?
好 行吧
Right. Okay.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
一切都会好起来的 我们一起面对 兄弟
It's gonna be all right. We're in this together, pal.
好吧 我会帮你的 帮你找到蒂娜和奎妮
Okay, I'm gonna help you out. I'm gonna help you find Tina, find Queenie
然后我们就会像往日一样开心了
and we'll all be happy again. Just like old times.
那个人是谁
Who is this guy?
他是我不经允许离开这个国家的唯一途径
He's the only way I can leave the country without documentation.
你不会晕船吧?
Now, you don't suffer from motion sickness, do you?
纽特 我并不是很适应坐船
I don't do well on boats, Newt.
不会有事的
You'll be fine.
赶快 一分钟后出发
Stir your stumps-it leaves in one minute!
50加隆
Fifty Galleons.
不,我们说好30的
No, we said thirty.
30是去法国的路费
Thirty to go to France,
另外20是封口费 不把纽特·斯卡曼德非法离境的事情说出去
twenty not to tell anyone, I seen Newt Scamander leaving the country illegally.
名声的代价啊 兄弟
Price of fame, pal.
10秒
Ten seconds.
八
Eight.
雅各布
Jacob.
七
Seven.
六
Six.
四、三、二
Four. Three. Two.
一
One.
我不喜欢那个门钥匙 纽特
I didn't like that Portkey, Newt.
你老这么说 跟着我
So you keep saying. Follow me.
混淆视听
Confundus.
来吧 咒语几分钟就失效了
Come on. That'll wear off in a few minutes.
踪迹显形
Appare vestigium.
嗅嗅飞来
Accio Niffler...
快去找 喂 快去找
Get looking. Oi! Get looking.
那是河童 是个日本水怪
That's a Kappa, That's a Japanese water demon.
蒂娜
Tina?
你找到了什么
What have you found?
还要吃土的吗
And we're licking the dirt now.
原形立现
Revelio.
纽特 这是什么
Newt... what made those?
那是驺吾
That is a Zouwu.
是中国的一种神兽 速度极快且力量强大
It's a Chinese creature. They are incredibly fast and incredibly powerful.
能够日行千里
They can travel a thousand miles in a day
一步就能跨越整座巴黎城
and this one could take you from one part of Paris to the next in a single leap.
哦 真棒
Oh, good boy.
雅各布 她来过
Jacob, she was here.
蒂娜在这里待过
Tina stood here.
你注意到了吗 她的脚特别细
She has incredibly narrow feet, have you noticed?
我还真没在意
Can't say that I have.
然后有人走向了她
Then someone came towards her.
(追踪咒)
Avenseguim.
-跟着那片羽毛 -什么
- Follow that feather. - What?
-雅各布 跟着羽毛 -跟着羽毛
- Jacob, follow the feather. - Follow the feather.
它在哪
Where is he?
嗅嗅飞来
Accio Niffler.
别提着桶了
Let go of the bucket!
对不起 我听不懂
I'm sorry, I don't know what you just said at all.
欢迎来到法国魔法部
Welcome to the French Ministry of Magic.
请问有何贵干
What is your business, please?
我要找蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩
I need to speak to Tina Goldstein.
她是个美国傲罗 在这里办案
She's an American Auror working on a case here.
这里没有蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩
We have no Tina Goldstein here.
不可能的 对不起 一定是哪里弄错了
No, it's... I'm sorry there must be some sort of mistake.
我知道她在巴黎 还给我寄了一张明信片
See, I know she's in Paris, she sent me a postcard.
我带来了 你看你能不能帮我找她
I brought it, I can show it to you. Maybe you can help me find her here?
就在这里
It's just in here.
该死 麻烦你等一下
Oh rabbits! If you can just wait one moment!
就在我包里 我肯定收起来了
I know it's in here somewhere. I definitely packed it.
放哪了
Where?
等一下
One second.
- 我们能不能至少停下来喝杯咖啡 或者... - 雅各布 还不是时候
- Could we at least stop for a coffee, or like a... - Not now, Jacob.
或是热巧克力 一下就好
Chocolate or... just for a second
走这边 快点
This way. Come on.
(法语)巧克力面包要吗 半块羊角面包或者糖果
Pain Au chocolat? Half a croissant, or like, a bonbon?
这边
This way.
雅各布
Jacob!
Jacob?
(法语)女士
Madame?
[法语]你还好吗 女士
(删剪片段)
她在家
She's home.
(法语)是谁啊
Qui est là?
(法语) 您的儿子来了 夫人
C'est votre fils, madame.
(法语) 你是谁
Qui est-ce?
你是厄玛吗
Are you Irma?
你是...你是厄玛·杜加尔德吗
Are you Irma Dugart?
抱歉 我的领养文件上写的是你的名字
I'm sorry. Your name is on my adoption paper.
能想起什么吗
Does this make sense?
你把我交给纽约的拜尔伯恩太太了
You gave me to Mrs. Bareborn in New York.
我不是你妈妈 我只是个仆人
I'm not your mother. I am just a servant.
你那时是个漂亮娃娃
You were a so beautiful baby.
现在长成帅小伙了
And you are a beautiful man.
我没想把你留在那儿
I didn't want to leave you there.
他们为什么不想要我
Why didn't they want me?
为什么我的领养文件上是你的名字
Why is your name on my adoption paper?
我带你去拜尔本太太那儿
I took you to Mrs. Bareborn
想着她能照顾你
because she was supposed to look after you.
她死了
She's dead.
那男孩反应如何？
How did the boy take it?
他很敏感
He's sensitive.
魔法部知道我失手了 一定不会高兴的
The ministry won't be happy when I tell them I missed.
-我清楚我的名声
-I know my reputation.
听我说 懦夫的反对是对勇者的赞扬
Listen to me. The disapproval of cowards is praise to the brave.
当巫师统治世界 你的姓名将伴随荣光
Your name will be written in glory when wizards rule the world.
这一天不会远了
And the clock is ticking faster.
照顾好克雷登斯 确保他安全
Watch over Credence. Keep him safe.
为了更伟大的利益
For the Greater Good.
你知道我想念奎妮什么吗
You know what I miss about Queenie?
一切
Everything.
我甚至怀念那些让我发疯的东西
I even miss the stuff that drove me nuts.
比如读心术
Like the mind reading.
她那样的人竟然会对我感兴趣...
I was happy to have someone like her even interested in...
我觉得很幸福
Anything I thought.
你明白我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
你说啥
Sorry?
我是说 你确定我们要找的人就在这里?
I was saying... You're sure the guy is here we're looking for?
肯定没错 羽毛是这么指示的
Definitely. The feather said so.
-那就是我们要找的人吗? -是的
-Is that the guy we're looking for? -Yes.
抱歉
Sorry.
(法语)您好... 您好 先生
Bonjour... Bonjour, monsieur.
等等,抱歉
Wait, no, sorry
我们只是想知道你是否遇到过我们的一个朋友...
We were just wondering if you came across a friend of ours.
蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩
Tina Goldstein.
先生们 巴黎可是座大城市
Messieurs, Paris is a large city.
她是个傲罗
She's an auror.
傲罗失踪的话魔法部会来找人 所以...
When an auror goes missing the Ministry tends to come looking, so...
我想我们还是回去上报失踪人口算了
I suppose it would probably be better if we reported her absence.
她个子高吗 皮肤黑吗
Is she tall? Dark?
是不是比较...
Rather...
-很严肃 -很漂亮
-Serious. -Beautiful.
我想说的是 她非常--非常漂亮
Yeah, what I meant to say was she's very-very pretty.
我想我昨晚见过这样的人
I think I saw someone like this last night.
也许我可以带你们去找她
Perhaps if I showed you where?
如果你不介意的话...
If you don't mind that would be...
-那太好了 -请随我来
-That would be lovely. -Sure.
蒂娜
Tina?
纽特
Newt!
除你武器
Expelliarmus
对不起 斯卡曼德先生
My apologies, Mr. Scamander.
克雷登斯一死 我就回来放你们出去
I shall return and release you once Credence is dead.
卡玛,等等！
Kama, wait!
不是他死 就是我亡
You see, whether he dies, or I do.
不不不
Oh, no.
哦不不不
No, no, no--
营救任务进行得可不太顺利
Well, that was not the best out for a rescue attempt.
这是一次营救行动吗 你刚刚害我丢掉唯一的线索
Oh this was a rescue attempt? You just lost me my only lead.
好吧 在我们出现前审讯怎么样
Well, how was the interrogation going before we turned up?
纽特
Newt!
干得好 皮克
Well done, Pick.
你说你需要这个人?
You said you needed this man?
对 我想这个人知道克雷登斯在哪里 斯卡曼德先生
Yes. I think this man knows where Credence is, Mr. Scamander.
那一定就是驺吾了
Well, that'll be the Zouwu.
来啊 纽特 快离开那儿
Come on, Newt, get out of there!
走了
Come on
你上次犯的最大的三个错误是什么?
What were the three biggest mistakes that you made last time?
被突袭而措手不及 先生
Caught by surprise, sir.
还有呢
What else?
是在破解咒前没有回避 老师
Didn't parry before counter-curse, sir.
很好 那最后一个...
Very good. And the last one...
最重要的那个错误是什么?
the most important one?
没从前两个错误里学到教训
Not learning from the first two.
这里是学校 你们无权闯入
This is a school, you've no right
我是魔法法律执行司的司长 我想去哪里都可以
I'm the Head of Magical Law Enforcement and I have the right to go wherever I please.
你们出去
Out of here.
你们和麦格教授一起出去吧
Go with Professor McGonagall, please.
他是我们最好的老师
He's the best teacher we've got.
-谢谢你 麦克拉根 -出去
- Thanks, McClaggan. - Get out!
走吧 麦克拉根
Come, McClaggan.
纽特·斯卡曼德现在在巴黎
Newt Scamander is in Paris.
真的吗
Really?
少装了 我知道他是奉你之命去的
Cut the pretense. I know he's there on your orders.
如果你有幸教过纽特
If you'd ever had the pleasure to teach him, you'd
你就会知道他不是个会乖乖听话的孩子
know Newt is not a great follower of orders.
你读过泰克 多多纳斯的预言录吗
You've read The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus??
多年前读过
Mmm. Many years ago.
"被残忍放逐之子 伤心且绝望之女"
"A son cruelly banished. Despair of the daughter."
-"伟大..." -我知道预言
- "Return..." - Yes, I know it.
有谣言说这个预言指的是默然者
There's a rumor this prediction refers to the Obscurial.
他们说格林德沃想要...
They say that Grindelwald wants...
一个出身名门的亲信 我听过传闻
As a highborn henchman. I've heard the rumor.
但无论默然者在哪现身 斯卡曼德都会及时出现
And yet, Scamander appears wherever the Obscurial goes,
去保护他
to protect him.
在此同时 你也结交了不少的国际友人
Meanwhile, you've built up quite the little network of international contacts.
不管你想监视我和我朋友多久
However long you keep me and my friends under surveillance,
都不会发现我们有任何地方违背你 特拉弗斯
you're not going to discover plots against you, Travers,
因为我们想要的是一样的 就是去打败格林德沃
because we want the same thing. The defeat of Grindelwald.
但我警告你 运用镇压和暴力的手段
But I warn you, your policies of suppression and violence
只会把人逼到他那一方去
are pushing supporters into his arms.
我对你的警告不感兴趣
I'm not interested in your warnings.
现在
Now...
我不想这么说 因为我不喜欢你
It pains me to say it because I don't like you...
但...
But...
能与他抗衡的巫师只有你
You are the only wizard who is his equal.
我需要你去对抗他
I need you to fight him.
我做不到
I can't.
是因为这个吗？
Because of this?
你与格林德沃曾经亲如兄弟
You and Grindelwald were as close as brothers.
我们比亲兄弟还亲
Oh, we were closer than brothers.
你愿意对抗他吗?
Will you fight him?
我不能
I can't.
那你已经选好你的立场了
Well, then you have chosen your side.
从现在起 我将知道你念的每一个咒语
From now on, I shall know every spell you cast.
我会派双倍人马监视你
I'm doubling the watch on you,
你也不再能教黑魔法防御术了
and you will no longer teach Defense Against the Dark Arts.
莉塔在哪？我们得赶往巴黎
Where's Leta? We need to go to Paris.
忒修斯
Theseus.
忒修斯 若格林德沃召集大型集会
Theseus, if Grindelwald calls a rally,
别试图去破坏
don't try and break it up.
别让特弗拉斯把你派进去
Don't let Travers send you in there.
若你曾相信过我...
If you ever trusted me...
忒修斯
Theseus.
Theseus!
光想到莱斯特兰奇这个姓就让我恶心
Even the name Lestrange makes me feel sick.
你也知道她每次放假都留在学校
You know she stays here every vacation.
她家人根本不希望她回家
Her family don't actually want her home.
也不怪他们 她实在太讨人厌
I don't blame them. She's so annoying.
你上个礼拜看到她了吗
Did you see her last week?
闭而不语
Oscausi!
麦格教授
Professor McGonagall!
莱斯特兰奇又违反校规了
Lestrange has done it again!
莱斯特兰奇 别跑
Lestrange, stop running!
-莱斯特兰奇！不听话的孩子！快停下！ -莉塔 回来
- Lestrange! Disobedient children. - Leta, come back!
别跑了 真让斯莱特林学院蒙羞
Stop! Shame on the House of Slytherin.
扣一百分 扣两百分
A hundred points! Two hundred!
给我回来 立马
Get back here, right now!
孩子们 停下来！你 停下来！回来！
Children, stop it! You, stop! Come back!
-别挡路 -她去哪了？
- Out of my way! - Where has she gone?
我想她往那边去了
I think she went that way!
老师 是莱斯特兰奇干的！她最坏了！
Miss, it was Lestrange. She's horrible.
斯卡曼德 你为什么不收拾行李
Scamander, why aren't you packing?
我不回家
I'm not going home.
为什么
Why not?
它需要我
He needs me.
它受伤了
He was hurt.
那是什么
What is that?
一只小渡鸦
A raven chick.
渡鸦不是你家族的标志么
Isn't the raven your family emblem?
对 没错
Yes, it is.
好了 纽特
All right, Newt.
勇敢一点
Be brave.
真是不同寻常
That's an unusual one.
所以斯卡曼德先生 在人生中最畏惧的是
So Mr. Scamander fears what more than anything else in the world?
被困在办公室里工作 老师
Having to work in an office, sir.
继续 纽特
Go ahead, Newt.
滑稽滑稽
Riddikulus.
漂亮
Well done.
干得好 莉塔
Good job. Leta.
就是一只博格特
It's only a Boggart.
它伤害不了你
It can't hurt you.
每个人都有害怕的东西
Everyone is scared of something.
我一直很期待这一刻
I've been looking forward to this.
我不想谈那件事
I don't want to talk about it.
它们认识我
They know me,
不然会躲起来
or they'd hide.
它们只在木质能制成魔杖的树上筑巢
They only nest in trees with wand-quality wood.
你知道吗
Did you know that?
它们也有很复杂的社交生活
And they have very complex social lives.
要是你观察得够久 就会发现的...
If you watch them for long enough, you realize...
嗨,莉塔,真让人讶异
Hello, Leta. This is a surprise.
会在教室里看到我?
Finding me in a classroom?
我是坏学生吗?
Was I such a bad student?
恰恰相反 你是我最聪明的学生之一
On the contrary, you were one of my cleverest.
我说坏学生 不是笨学生
I said "bad," not "stupid."
别费心回答了
Don't bother answering.
我知道你没喜欢过我
I know you never liked me.
那你错了
You're wrong.
我从不认为你坏
I never thought you bad.
那你是个例外 所有人都这么觉得
You were alone, then. Everybody else did.
而且他们是对的
And they were right.
我的确很坏
I was wicked.
莉塔 我了解那些
Leta, I know how painful
关于你弟弟考乌斯的谣言 令你有多痛苦
the rumors about your brother Corvus must be for you.
不 你不了解
No, you don't.
除非你也有个死去的弟弟
Not unless you had a brother who died, too.
我妹妹不在了
In my case, it was my sister.
你爱她吗
Did you love her?
我应该更爱她的
Not as well as I should have done.
让自己释怀是从来不会晚
Never too late to free yourself.
有人说 忏悔是一种解脱 能让你如释重负
Confession is a relief, I'm told. A great weight lifted.
多年来悔恨一直伴随着我
Regret is my constant companion.
别让它也变成你的心魔
Do not let it become yours.
不用了 谢谢
Oh! No, thank you.
好了
Well...
你人实在太好了
You've been really kind,
我姐姐蒂娜大概急着找我找疯了
but my sister Tina's probably worried sick about me.
像是到处乱敲门之类的
You know, banging on all the doors and things,
我还是走好了
so I think I'd better be going.
但你还没见到主人
But you haven't met your host.
噢 你结婚了?
Oh, are you married?
应该说...
Let's say,
我完全效忠于他
deeply committed.
你看我就是分不清你到底是开玩笑还是...
You see, I can't tell if you're making a joke or if you're just...
法国人都这样
French.
噢
Oh.
喂 别闹了
Hey, knock it off.
你别过来
You stay right there.
我知道你是谁
I know what you are.
奎妮
Queenie.
我们不是来伤害你的
We are not here to hurt you.
我们只想帮助你
We only want to help you.
你离家太远了
You're so very, very far away from home.
远离一切你所深爱的事物 远离你的舒适圈
Far away from everything you love, everything that is comfortable.
我不想看你受伤害
I would never see you harmed.
永远不想
Ever.
你姐姐是一名傲罗并不是你的错
It is not your fault that your sister is an Auror.
我希望你现在能与我同一阵线
I wish you were working with me now
努力让世界能容许巫师光明正大的生活
towards a world where we wizards were free to live openly.
能择其所爱
To love freely.
你从未伤害任何人
You are an innocent.
你走吧
So go now.
离开这地方
Leave this place.
(删剪片段)
原来你在这
There you are.
特拉弗斯到底想干什么? 他的行为太过分了
What did Travers want? Absolutely outrageous behavior.
那样冲进一所学校
Marching into a school like that.
那不算什么
It was all very mundane,
不好意思 米勒娃 我还有很多作业要批改
I'm fine, sorry, Minerva, lot of marking.
嘿纽特 兄弟 额...
Hey, uh, Newt, buddy. Uh...
蒂娜在上面 她就孤单一人
Tina's up here. She's all by her lonesome,
所以你要不要上来陪陪她?
and, uh, maybe you want to come up and keep her company?
我四处找食物可一直都没找到
Uh, I've been looking for food, and I ain't found any,
所以我觉得我要上楼碰碰运气
so I guess I'm gonna go upstairs and try my luck
或许阁楼也得看看
in, oh, I don't know, the attic.
你会没事的
You're all right.
力劲松懈
Relashio.
好吧
Okay.
它对白鲜的反应很好
She's responded well to the Dittany.
它天生就爱乱跑
She was born to run, you see.
但我想它只是有点缺乏自信
But I think she's...She's just lacking in confidence.
斯卡曼德先生 你皮箱里有东西
Mr. Scamander, have you got anything in your case
能叫醒这个人吗
that might help revive this man?
我得盘问他
I need to question him.
我想他知道克雷登斯的真实身份 而他手上的伤疤
I think he knows who Credence really is. And the scars on his hand
-代表他曾立下牢不可破咒 -牢不可破咒
- suggest an Unbreakable Vow. - An Unbreakable Vow.
我也注意到了
Yeah, I noticed that, too.
荧光闪烁
Lumos.
那是什么?
What was that?
那个下水道里一定有水龙
There must be a Water Dragon in that sewer.
它们身上常常有这种寄生虫 你看 它们...
They carry these parasites, you see. They, um...
-雅各布 -咋了
- Jacob. - Yeah?
在我皮箱的夹层中,有一支镊子
In my case, in the pocket there, you'll find a pair of tweezers.
镊子?
Tweezers?
-就是细细尖尖... -尖尖的工具
- They're thin, pointy... - Little pointy things.
我知道镊子是什么
Yes, I know what tweezers are.
你应该不会想看这个场面的
All right. You might not want to watch this.
我没问题
I can handle it.
出来吧
Come out.
来吧 你没事
Come on. You're all right.
- 呃 - 来啊 我拉住了
- Ew. - Come on. I got you.
雅各布 能帮我拿着吗
Jacob, will you take that for me?
透抽
Calamari.
一定要杀了他
Must kill him.
谁
Who?
克雷登斯?
Credence?
可能要几小时才会恢复
It may take him a few hours to recover.
那寄生虫的毒性颇强
That parasite's poison is quite strong.
我必须回魔法部去汇报进度
I have to go back to the Ministry with what I've got.
很高兴再次见到你 斯卡曼德先生
It's nice to see you again, Mr. Scamander.
唉唉 稍等一下 好吗
Hey. Hey . Hold on a second, will ya?
稍等 等一下
Hold on. Hold on.
别走蒂娜
Wait! Tina.
你没提火蜥蜴吧?
You didn't mention salamanders, did you?
我没有 她就这样走了 我不懂
No, I didn't. She just ran. I don't know...
你要去追啊
So you chase after her.
蒂娜 拜托你听我说
Tina. Please, just listen to me.
斯卡曼德 我得去跟魔法部汇报
Mr. Scamander, I need to go talk to the Ministry.
我知道你对于傲罗的看法
I know how you feel about Aurors.
我在那些信里的言辞可能有一些过激
I may have been a little strong
in the way that I expressed myself in that letter.
你用的是什么词来着? 一群虚伪又野心勃勃的人
What was the exact phrase? "A bunch of careerist hypocrites"?
很抱歉 我不欣赏那些
I'm sorry, but I can't admire people
对于一切不了解或者恐惧的东西就起了杀心的人
whose answer to everything that they fear or misunderstand is "kill it."
我就是一名傲罗 然而我并不是那样的人
I'm an Auror and I don't.
是的 因为你是中间那个头
Yes, I know. That's because you've gone middle head.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
这个措辞来自如尼纹蛇的三个头
It's an expression derived from the three heads of the Runespoor.
中间那个头最有远见
So the middle one is the visionary.
除你以外整个欧洲的傲罗都想要格雷登斯死
Now, every Auror in Europe wants Credence dead, except you.
所以你是中间那个头
You've gone middle head.
还有谁会用这种表述吗 斯卡曼德先生
Who else uses that expression, Mr. Scamander?
大概只有我会用吧
I think it might just be me.
是格林德沃 他在召集他的追随者
It's Grindelwald. He's calling his followers.
太迟了 格林德沃是冲着格雷登斯来的
It's too late. Grindelwald has come for Credence.
-搞不好已经找到他了 -还不算迟
- He might already have him. - It's not too late.
我们还是能先找到他
We can still get to him first.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
法国魔法部
The French Ministry of Magic.
克雷登斯最不可能去那里了
That's the last place Credence would go.
魔法部里藏有一个盒子
There's a box hidden in the Ministry, Tina.
它能告诉我们克雷登斯的真实身份
It's a box that can tell us who Credence really is.
盒子? 你在讲什么?
A box? What are you talking about?
相信我
Trust me.
你想出来吗? 就一小会儿
You wanna come out, just for a little while?
可以自由走动
You can be free.
克雷登斯
Credence.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
从你身上?
From you?
什么也不要
Nothing.
我能给你什么?
For you?
我未曾拥有的一切
Everything I never had.
但你又想要什么 孩子?
But what is it you want, my boy?
我想知道我究竟是谁
I want to know who I am.
你会在这里找到你真实身份的证据
This is where you will find proof of your true identity.
今晚到拉雪兹神父公墓 你会知道事实
Come to Père Lachaise tonight, and you will discover the truth.
父亲 你为何要逼我
Father, why did you make me...
等等
Wait...
Wait.
我恐怕这屋子里没什么吃的
I'm afraid we keep no food in the house.
你是鬼吗?
Are you a ghost?
不
No.
不 我是活人
No. I'm alive.
但我是炼金术士 所以长生不老
But I'm an alchemist and therefore immortal.
你看起来绝对不超过375岁
You don't look a day over 375.
很抱歉我们没有敲门
I'm sorry that we didn't knock.
不 没关系
No. No matter.
阿不思有跟我说会有朋友造访
Albus told me some friends might be dropping in.
我是尼可?勒梅
Nicolas Flamel.
我是雅各布·科沃斯基
Jacob Kowalski.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's all right.
-我不是... -哦 哦
- I didn't... - Oh... Oh!
终于有些动静了
At last, we see some development.
对 我以前看过这个东西
Yeah. I've seen one of these before.
是在园游会
It was at the fair.
有个戴面纱的女人
There was this dame there, and she had a veil,
我给她五分钱 然后她预言我的未来
and I gave her a nickel, and she told me about my future.
其实她漏掉好多东西
And she missed out on quite a bit, actually.
等等 我认识他 是克雷登斯那小子
Wait a minute, I know him. That's the kid. That's Credence.
老天
Jeez.
嘿
Hey... Hey!
那是奎妮 她在那儿 嗨 宝贝
That's Queenie. There she is. Hi, baby.
这是哪 是不是在这附近?
Where is this? Is this here?
是的 这是莱斯特兰奇家族的墓
Yes. This is the Lestrange tomb.
坐落在拉雪兹神父公墓内
It lies in the cemetery of Père Lachaise.
我来了 宝贝 别走开
I'm coming, baby. Stay right there.
谢谢你 勒梅先生
Thank you, Mr. Flamel.
-啊！ -哦 对不起 对不起 好吧
- Ouch. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay.
帮我顾一下章鱼哥 哦不
Oh, look after Mr. Tentacles for me. Oh, no.
抱歉 我得走了
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
请你千万不能去公墓
Please, you mustn't go to the cemetery.
发生什么事了?
What's happening?
完全照他说的发生了
Exactly what he said would happen.
格林德沃今晚会在公墓集会
Grindelwald rallies at the cemetery tonight,
肯定会有伤亡
and there will be death.
那你得过去
Then you gotta go.
什么 我已经两百年没动过手了
What? I haven't seen action in 200 years.
勒梅 你必须得去 我们对你有信心
Flamel, you can do this. We believe in you.
盒子在族谱档案室里 蒂娜
The box is in the Ancestral Records room, Tina.
所以 应该在地下三楼
So it's three floors down.
那是复方汤剂吗
Is that Polyjuice?
这些只够我混进去
It's just enough to get me inside.
-是谁... -我哥哥 忒修斯
- Who... - It's my brother, Theseus.
他是个傲罗 还很爱抱人
He's an Auror and a hugger.
怎么了
What's happening?
格林德沃要举行集会
Grindelwald's rallying.
地点不知道 但估计是今晚
We don't know where, but we think it's tonight.
-小心点 -当然
- Be careful. - Of course.
-答应我要你一定要小心 -我当然会小心的
- Promise me you'll be careful. - Of course. I'm gonna be careful.
听好 我希望是由我告诉你
Listen, I want you to hear this from me.
他们认为克雷登斯 可能是你失踪的弟弟
They think that Credence boy might be your missing brother.
-我弟弟已经死了 -我知道
- My brother is dead. - I know.
-他死了 -我知道
- He died. - I know.
-这话还要说几次 忒修斯? -档案会证明一切
- How many times, Theseus? - And the records will prove that.
-好吗 档案不会说谎 -忒修斯
- Okay? They can't lie. - Theseus.
我要你逮捕参与集会的每一人 若反抗...
I want every person at that rally arrested. If they resist...
长官 如果我们逼得太紧
Sir, forgive me, but if we go in too heavy,
-不就助长了... -照做就行了
- don't we run the risk of adding to... - Just do it.
我猜你无法在法国魔法部内幻影移形吧?
I don't suppose you can Disapparate on Ministry premises in France, can you?
不行
Nope.
真可惜
Pity.
-纽特 -是 我知道 我知道
- Newt! - Yes, I know. I know it's...
纽特
Newt!
- 哦 - 那个是你哥哥?
- Oh! - That's your brother?
我想我在信中提过
So I think I may have mentioned in my letters
我们俩的关系很复杂
that we have quite a complicated relationship.
纽特 停下来
Newt, stop!
-他想杀你吗? -经常
- Does he wanna kill you? - Frequently.
别跑了
Enough!
他需要控制他的脾气
He needs to control his temper.
我觉得这可能是我此生最棒的时刻
I think that might have been the best moment of my life.
奎妮
Queenie.
奎妮 甜心
Queenie, honey.
别 别动
Don't. Don't move.
(有何贵干?)
这位是莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Yes, this is Leta Lestrange.
我是她的...
And, uh, I'm her...
未婚夫
Fiancé.
(进去吧)
谢谢
Thank you.
蒂娜 关于未婚夫那件事
Tina, about that fiancée business...
抱歉 我该恭喜你
Oh, sorry. Yeah, I should have congratulated you.
-不 那是... -荧光闪烁
- No, that's... - Lumos.
莱斯特兰奇
Lestrange.
蒂娜 关于莉塔
Tina, about Leta...
是的 我说了替你开心
Yes, I've just said I am happy for you.
我没有 拜托别不开心
No, I don't... Please, don't be happy.
不 抱歉 我不是...
No. Sorry. I don't...
很显然我...
Obviously, I...
很显然我希望你开心
Obviously, I want you to be...
我也听说你现在很开心 那很棒
And I hear that you are now. Which is wonderful.
抱歉 我想说的是 我希望你开心
Sorry, what I'm trying to say is, I want you to be happy,
但我不想你因为我开心而开心 因为我没有...
but I don't want you to be happy that I'm happy, because I'm not.
开心
Happy.
或是订婚
Or engaged.
-什么? -那本蠢杂志搞错了
- What? - It was a mistake in a stupid magazine.
是我哥要娶莉塔 婚期定在六月六号
My brother's marrying Leta, June the 6th.
我是伴郎
I'm supposed to be best man,
说起来有点可笑
which is sort of mildly hilarious.
他认为你是来横刀夺爱的吗
Does he think you're here to win her back?
你是来横刀夺爱的吗
Are you here to win her back?
不 我来这里...
No, I'm here...
你知道 你的眼睛真的...
You know, your eyes really are...
真的什么?
Are what?
有人叫我不要说
I'm not supposed to say.
-我剪下你的照片 -纽特 我读了你的书
- I cut a picture of you... - Newt, I read your book and...
-等等 你读了... -你有吗?
- Wait, did you read... - Did you?
我把这剪下
I cut this, um...
就是报纸上面你的照片
It's just a picture of you from the paper,
很有趣 因为在报纸上你的眼睛...
but it's interesting 'cause your eyes in newsprint...
看你本人时 你眼睛里有种光辉 就像...
See, in reality they have this effect in them, Tina. It's like...
像是黑水中燃烧的火焰
It's like fire in water, in dark water.
我只曾在动物身上见过
And I've only ever seen that...
我只曾在动物身上见过 那就是...
I've only ever seen that in...
火蜥蜴
Salamanders.
来
Come.
莱斯特兰奇
Lestrange.
(资料移至拉雪兹神父公墓内的 莱斯特兰奇家族陵墓)
即刻旋转
Circumrota.
你好 纽特
Hello, Newt.
你好 莉塔
Hello, Leta.
嗨
Hi.
哦不
Oh, no.
那是什么猫？
What kind of cats are those?
那些不是猫
Uh, these aren't cats.
是玛达戈猫 一种灵性生物
They're Matagots. They're spirit familiars.
它们守卫魔法部
They guard the Ministry.
它们不会伤人 除非...
But they won't hurt you unless you...
昏昏倒地
Stupefy!
除非你先攻击它们
Unless you attack them.
糟糕
Oops.
-莉塔 -通通复原
- Leta. - Reverte.
速速飞来
Accio!
齐齐高攀
Ascendio!
等等 别闹了等一下 拜托
Okay. Wait. Hold it there, please.
别这样
Come on.
好了
All right.
好了 等等
Okay, wait.
你,退后,快点,快让开
You, go back. Move! Out of the way!
若杀考乌斯也得杀了你 我会动手
If I must kill you as well as Corvus, I shall.
住手
Stop!
尤瑟夫
Yusuf.
真的是你吗
Is that really you?
我的妹妹?
My little sister?
所以他是你哥哥
So he's your brother.
我是谁?
Who am I?
我不知道
I don't know.
我厌倦了无名无过往的人生
I'm tired of living with no name and no history.
跟我说我的故事 之后任凭处置
Just tell me my story, then you can end it.
你的故事就是我们的故事
Your story is our story.
我们的故事
Our story.
不 尤瑟夫
No, Yusuf.
我父亲穆斯塔法·卡玛
My father was Mustafa Kama.
是塞内加尔裔最知名的纯血巫师
Pure-blood of Senegalese descent and most accomplished.
我母亲劳瑞娜
My mother, Laurena,
同样是出身名门的著名美女
was equally highbred, a noted beauty.
他们深爱彼此
They were deeply in love.
他俩认识一名出身法国纯血望族的男人
They knew a man of great influence from a famous French pure-blood family.
他贪恋她的美色
He desired her.
(法语)妈妈
Maman. Maman!
莱斯特兰奇用夺魂咒勾引并绑架她
Lestrange used the Imperius Curse to seduce and abduct her.
我试着阻止 但他攻击了我
I tried to prevent it, but he attacked me.
那是我最后一次看到她
That was the last time I ever saw her.
她生下一名女婴 难产而死
She died giving birth to a little girl.
就是你
You.
她的死讯把我父亲逼疯
The news of her death drove my father insane.
在咽下最后一口气前
With his dying breath,
我父亲要我为他复仇
my father charged me to seek revenge.
杀死莱斯特兰奇世上最爱的人
Kill the person Lestrange loves best in the world.
我一开始以为很容易
I thought at first it'd be easy.
他只有一个近亲
He had only one close relative.
就是你
You.
但是他...
But he...
说吧
Say it.
他从没爱过你
He never loved you.
她死后不足三个月 他就再婚了
He remarried, and not three months after her death.
他既不爱她 也不爱你
He loved her no more than he had loved you.
但他的儿子考乌斯随后出生
But then his son, Corvus, was born at last.
那个从不知爱为何物的人 突然充满父爱
And that man who had never known love was filled with it.
他唯一在乎的
All he cared about
只有小考乌斯
was little Corvus.
所以是真的?
So this is the truth?
我是考乌斯·莱斯特兰奇?
I am Corvus Lestrange?
-对 -不对
- Yes. Yes. - No. No.
知道穆斯塔法·卡玛之子 立誓报仇后
Realizing that Mustafa Kama's son had sworn revenge,
你父亲要把你藏在我找不到的地方
your father sought to hide you where I couldn't find you.
他将你托付给仆人 搭船前往美国
So he confided you to his servant, who boarded a ship for America.
-他的确送考乌斯去美国 但... -他的仆人伊尔玛·杜加尔德
- He did send Corvus to America, but... - His servant, Irma Dugard,
是个混血精灵
was a half-elf.
她的法力太弱
Her magic was weak,
留下的踪迹让我无法追踪
and therefore left no trace I could follow.
我终于发现你如何逃脱时
I had only just discovered how you had escaped
我收到出乎意料外的消息
when I received news I never expected.
船在大海中沉没了
The ship had gone down at sea.
但你幸存下来了 不是吗?
But you survived, didn't you?
总之 有人将你从水中拉上来
Somehow, someone had pulled you from the water.
"被残忍放逐之子 伤心且绝望之女"
"A son cruelly banished Despair of the daughter
"伟大复仇者的回归 从水中携带着羽翼"
Return, great avenger, With wings from the water."
那里站着伤心且绝望之女
There stands the despairing daughter.
你是长着羽翼的渡鸦从海中回归 而我...
You are the winged raven, returned from the sea,
我 我是身负灭门血仇的复仇者
but I'm the avenger of my family's ruin.
我同情你 考乌斯
I pity you, Corvus.
但你非死不可
But you must die.
考乌斯·莱斯特兰奇早就死了 是我杀了他
Corvus Lestrange is already dead! I killed him!
速速飞来
Accio!
我父亲家有着非常奇妙的族谱
My father owned a very strange family tree.
上面只记录男性
It only recorded the men.
家族的女性以花朵代表
The women in my family were recorded as flowers.
(考乌斯·莱斯特兰奇)
美丽
Beautiful.
孤立
Separate.
我父亲把我和考乌斯一起送往美国
My father sent me to America with Corvus.
伊尔玛假扮带着孙子们旅行的奶奶
Irma was to pose as a grandmother with two grandchildren.
考乌斯总是哭个不停
Corvus never stopped crying.
有任何消息吗?
Do you have any news?
所有人员回工作岗位
All hands to station!
立刻返回岗位
Run to station!
我从没想过伤害他
I never wanted to hurt him.
我只是想要摆脱他
I only wanted to be free of him.
哪怕只是一下
Just for a moment.
一下下就好
Just a single moment.
把他给我
Give him to me.
各位 前往救生船
Everyone, to the lifeboats!
他们叫大家穿救生衣
They want us to put on life jackets.
你不是故意的 莉塔
You didn't mean to do it, Leta.
所以不是你的错
So it wasn't your fault.
不 纽特
Oh, Newt.
你总能在怪物身上发现可爱之处
You never met a monster you couldn't love.
莉塔
Leta...
你知道克雷登斯的真实身分吗
Do you know who Credence really is?
在你调包的时候
Did you know when you swapped them?
不知道
No.
奎妮
Queenie?
他们是纯血巫师
They're pure-bloods.
专门以杀我们这种人为乐
They kill the likes of us for sport.
奎妮
Queenie?
雅各布
Jacob!
甜心 你来了 嗨
Honey, you're here! Hi!
嗨 甜心
Hi, hon. Hi.
甜心 我真抱歉
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
我不该一走了之 我好爱你
I never should have done it. I love you so much.
你也知道我爱你 对吧?
And you know that I love you, right?
对
Yeah.
很好 那我们闪人吧
Good. Let's get the hell outta here.
不 等等 等一下
Oh, no, wait a second.
我想先听听他要说什么
I just thought maybe we could hear him first.
听听就好 如此而已
Just listen. That's all.
你在讲什么?
What are you talking about?
这是陷阱
It's a trap.
对
Yeah.
奎妮 族谱 只为了引我们入陷阱
Queenie, the family tree. It's all been bait.
我们得快想办法立刻离开
We have to find a way out of here right now.
你去找其他人
You go find the others.
你呢?
What are you gonna do?
我会见招拆招的
I'll think of something.
兄弟们 姐妹们
My brothers, my sisters,
朋友们
my friends,
你们热烈的掌声不该献给我
the great gift of your applause is not for me. No.
而该献给自己
It is for yourselves.
你们来此是因为心里向往
You came today because of a craving
并深切了解
and a knowledge
墨守陈规对我们已不再管用
that the old ways serve us no longer.
你们来此是因为渴望新的东西
You came today because you crave something new.
不同的局面
Something different.
很多人说
It is said
我痛恨不懂魔法之人
that I hate les non-Magiques.
麻瓜们
The Muggles.
-害虫 -麻鸡
- Vermin! - The No-Maj.
不施咒语者
The Can't-Spells.
我不恨他们
I do not hate them.
完全不恨
I do not.
因为我不是为仇恨而战
For I do not fight out of hatred.
我认为麻瓜并不是更低级
I say the Muggles are not lesser,
而是属性不同
but other.
并非一文不值
Not worthless,
而是价值不同
but of other value.
不是不堪大用 而是别有用途
Not disposable, but of a different disposition.
魔法天赋
Magic blooms
只在少数人身上绽放
only in rare souls.
只降临在对生命 有着更高追求者的身上
It is granted to those who live for higher things.
若将世界交给我们统治 必能嘉惠全人类
Oh, and what a world we would make for all of humanity.
因我们全然为自由
We who live for freedom,
为真理
for truth,
为爱而生
and for love.
听他演说又不犯法
It isn't illegal to listen to him.
对群众要慎用武力
Use minimum force on the crowd.
我们不能成为他口中的那种人
We mustn't be what he says we are.
大限已到 该向大家展示我所预见的未来了
The moment has come to share my vision of the future
若不揭竿起义
that awaits if we do not rise up
若不顺应天命将是何等境地
and take our rightful place in the world.
不要再打仗了
Not another war.
这就是我们要对抗的
That is what we are fighting.
这就是敌人
That is the enemy.
他们的狂妄自大
Their arrogance.
他们的渴求权力
Their power lust.
他们的粗鄙残暴
Their barbarity.
在他们将枪杆转向我们前 还有多少时间?
How long will it take before they turn their weapons on us?
大家听我说就好 不要轻举妄动
Do nothing when I speak of this.
你们务必保持冷静
You must remain calm
控制自己情绪
and contain your emotions.
我们之中混杂了傲罗
There are Aurors here among us.
靠近点 巫师兄弟们 加入我们
Come closer, brother wizards. Join us.
按兵不动
Do nothing.
不要动武
And no force.
他们杀死我许多追随者
They have killed many of my followers.
那是事实
It is true.
他们在纽约拘禁我 折磨我
They confined me and tortured me in New York.
他们滥杀女巫及巫师同胞
They had struck down their fellow witches and wizards.
只因他们犯下追求真理的罪
For the simple crime of seeking the truth.
只因渴求自由
For wanting freedom.
你们的愤怒和复仇的渴望 是正常的
Your anger, your desire for revenge is natural.
不
No!
将这名年轻勇士的遗体 交还给她家人
Take this young warrior back to her family.
幻影移形吧
Disapparate.
都走吧
Leave.
离开后记得传话出去
Go forth from this place and spread the word.
滥用暴力的人不是我们
It is not we who are violent.
我们拿下他
Let's take him.
傲罗们 走进来加入我的行列
Aurors, join me in this circle.
宣告你的忠诚
Pledge to me
顺我者昌
your eternal allegiance,
逆我者亡
or die.
唯有在这里才能享有自由
Only here shall you know freedom.
唯有在这里才能了解真我
Only here shall you know yourself.
闪开！ 快跑！
Move! Run! Run!
要遵守游戏规则 不准作弊 孩子们
Play by the rules! No cheating, children.
他知道我是谁
He knows who I am.
他知晓你的身世 但不了解你的为人
He knows what you were born, not who you are!
克雷登斯
Credence!
奎妮 甜心 你清醒点
Queenie, honey. Queenie. You gotta wake up.
雅各布
Jacob.
他就是答案
He's the answer.
我们与他目标一致
He wants what we want.
-不 -是的
- No. - Yeah.
这一切都是为了你 克雷登斯
This has all been for you, Credence.
陪我一起去
Walk with me.
甜心 不
Hon. No!
陪我一起去
Walk with me!
你疯了
You're crazy.
奎妮
Queenie.
不
No!
奎妮 不要
Queenie, don't do it!
奎妮
Queenie.
Queenie!
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
你觉得邓布利多会为你哀悼吗
Do you think Dumbledore will mourn for you?
格林德沃 住手
Grindelwald! Stop!
莉塔
Leta...
我想我认识你
This one I believe I know.
莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Leta Lestrange.
被全体巫师界仇视
Despised entirely amongst wizards,
无人疼爱 饱受霸凌
unloved, mistreated,
但仍勇敢 非常勇敢
yet brave, so very brave.
是时候该回家了
Time to come home.
我爱你
I love you.
快走
Go!
我讨厌巴黎
I hate Paris.
大家一起围成圆形 魔杖遁地
Together, in a circle. Your wand into the earth.
否则巴黎将毁于一旦
Or all Paris will be destroyed.
万咒皆终
Finite!
我早就选好一边站了
I've chosen my side.
过来 过来抱抱 过来抱抱
Come here. I've got you. I've got you.
我想最好让他俩单独谈谈
I think it's best if he speaks to him alone.
(奥地利 纽蒙迦德城堡)
他还是很怕我吗
Is he frightened of me still?
讲话要小心
You need to be careful.
他不确定自己的选择是否正确
He's not sure he made the right choice.
要温柔地对待他
Be very gentle with him.
我有礼物送给你 孩子
I have a gift for you, my boy.
是真的吗
Is it true?
莉塔的事
About Leta?
是
Yes.
太遗憾了
I'm so sorry.
这是血盟 对吗?
It's a blood pact, isn't it?
你俩立誓永不与对方为敌
You swore not to fight each other.
以梅林之名 你是怎么拿到...
How in the name of Merlin did you manage to get...
格林德沃向来低估 他觉得不起眼的小东西
Grindelwald doesn't seem to understand the nature of the things he considers simple.
有办法销毁吗
Can you destroy it?
或许吧
Maybe.
或许
它会想要来杯茶吗
Would he like a cup of tea?
它会想喝牛奶
He'll have some milk.
得把银汤匙藏好
Hide the teaspoons.
你多次遭遇最残忍的背叛
You have suffered the most heinous of betrayals,
而且大多是由至亲手足
most purposely bestowed upon you by your own blood.
跟你血脉相承的人刻意加注于你
Your own flesh and blood.
如同他以你的痛苦为乐一般
And just as he has celebrated your torment,
你的哥哥还想要赶尽杀绝
your brother seeks to destroy you.
你家族传说,若是任何成员有难
There is a legend in your family that a phoenix will come to any member
就会有凤凰来搭救
who is in dire need.
这是你与生俱来的权利 孩子
It is your birthright, my boy.
我现在
As is
重新替你正名
the name I now restore to you.
奥睿利乌斯
Aurelius.
奥睿利乌斯·邓不利多
Aurelius Dumbledore.
我们会因为重整世界 而一起名留青史
We will go down in history together as we remake this world.